

RAKHMAN ABDURAKHMANOV

• DETAILS •

Tbilisi Georgia +995555752959 crystallographer@skiff.com

• LINKS •

LinkedIn

GitHub

• SKILLS •

Bootstrap

CSS

Docker Git

HTML

JavaScript

jQuery

Linux

Node.js

React

TypeScript

• HOBBIES •

Fitness, Traveling, Cooking, Eating, Nature Photography, Coding, Sleeping, Bowling, Walking, Pool & Billiards, Landscape Photography, Chess, Listening to Music, Reading.

• LANGUAGES •

Azerbaijanian
English
Georgian
Russian

PROFILE

My journey into front-end development began at a hackathon organized by axmit. I participated in it together with a team of other guys. We were in the top three finalists and were invited to work.

At axmit I worked on many outsourced projects such as Zelos (https://getzelos.com) and Activatica (https://activatica.org).

After that, I got a job at inter://so as the main front-end developer in their startup project.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Front-end Developer at axmit, Petrozavodsk

June 2019 — October 2020

At axmit I worked on many outsourcing projects, such as Zelos (https://getzelos.com) and Activatica (https://activatica.org). I was mostly involved in project support. I mean fixing bugs and adding new features.

Front-end Developer at inter://so, Petrozavodsk

February 2022 — September 2022

At inter://so I worked as the main front-end developer on their startup project. I started the project from scratch and was responsible for the project architecture and technologies used.

EDUCATION

Bachelor, Petrozavodsk State University, Petrozavodsk

September 2014 — June 2018

Specialization in electronics and nanoelectronics.

Master, Petrozavodsk State University

September 2018 — June 2020

Specialization in mathematics.